There are three things you must never say in a job interview.
Number one, do not say, I am nervous.
Because if you say you are nervous, the hiring manager will think you lack the confidence
to do your job competently.
Number two, you should never say anything negative about your former employer, co-workers
or boss.
If you do say anything negative, the hiring manager might think it's you who has the problem.
And then finally, the third thing you should never say in a job interview is that you
are a perfectionist.
Especially when answering the interview question, what is your biggest weakness?
Instead, tell them that your biggest weakness is the fact that you are not very good at public
speaking.
But if there are any opportunities in the role to give talks to your team, you would
love to give it a try.